Finding aid to the Iva Dee Hiatt papers CA.MS.00281
Smith College Archives
- Repertory: Various Repertoires, 1967-74; undated (Box 7)
- Repertory: Victorie: Mira Pro Defunctis (c.1548-1611) (Box 7)
- Repertory: Women in Music (Box 7)
- Personal: Assorted School Certificates, School Letters (Box 7)
- Personal: School Notebooks-Contents, undated (Box 7)
- Personal: Diplomas-Grade and High School (Box 7)
- Personal: Senior and Junior High School-Yearbook and Graduation Announcement, 1933; 1936 (Box 7)
- Personal: "Sacred Music of Monteverdi" Iva Dee Hiatt's Dissertation, 1948 (Box 7)
- Personal: News Clippings and Critiques (Box 7)
- Personal: Passports, 1951-75 (Box 7)
- Personal: Membership Cards, Contributions (Box 7)
- Personal: Diaries, Notebooks (Box 7)
- Personal: Address Books (Box 7)
- Personal: Verses 1 of 2 (Box 7)
- Personal: Verses 2 of 2 (Box 7)
- Personal: Verses and Papers Found in Stamp Book (Box 7)
- Personal: Pilot Logs, 1940-41 (Box 7)
- Personal: Auto Insurance and Title (Box 7)
- Personal: List of Assets and Smith Evaluations (Box 7)
- Personal: Resumes (Box 7)
- Personal: Sabbatical Leave (Box 7)
- Personal: Honors (Box 7)
- Personal: Honors-Appalachian State Scholarship, 1978 (Box 7)
- Personal: International Communication Agency, 1979 (Box 7)
- Personal: New England Conservatory of Music, 1979 (Box 7)
- Personal: Smith Retirement, 1979 (Box 7)
- Personal: Reunion Display, 1979 (Box 7)
- Personal: A.L.S. Material (Health) (Box 7)
- Personal: Obituaries, 1980 (Box 7)
- Personal: Memorial Service, 1980 (Box 7)
- Personal: Memorial Service and Haitt Fund (Box 7)
- Personal: Family History (Box 7)
- Personal: Correspondence from Fred and Iva L. (Box 7)
- Personal: Fred W. Haitt 1 of 2 (Box 7)
- Personal: Fred W. Haitt 2 of 2 (Box 7)
- Personal: Childhood-Background and Adoption (Box 7)
- Personal: Iva Lindley Hiatt 1 of 2 (Box 7)
- Personal: Iva Lindley Hiatt 2 of 2 (Box 7)
- Personal: Iva Lindley Hiatt-Death, 1938 (Box 7)
- Personal: Postage Stamp Book (Box 8)
  General
  RESTRICTED
- Personal: Miss Hiatt's Director Gloves (Box 8)
- Personal: Booklets and Information on Finance, Investments, Taxes, Stocks, Life Insurance (Box 8)
- Non Smith: Music Department Letter, 1977 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: Chamber Society for Early Music (C.S.E.M.)-Music (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M.-Music (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M.-News Clippings, 1960s (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M.-News Clippings, 1970s &amp; undated (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M.-Notes, undated (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M.-Performers (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M.-Repertory Ideas from Artists' Management Association, 1966-75 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M.-Repertory Ideas from Artists' Management Association, 1967-73 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M.-Repertory Ideas from Artists' Management Association, undated (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M..-Repertory Ideas from Artists' Management Association-Press Releases (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M.-Programs, 1961-64 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: Chamber Society for Early Music (C.S.E.M.), 1965 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M.-Programs, Misc., 1966 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M.-Programs, Misc., 1967 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M., 1968 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M.-Programs, Misc., 1969 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M.-Programs, Reports, Routine Business, 1970 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M.-Programs, Reports, Routine Business, 1972 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M., 1972 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M., 1973 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M., 1974 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M.-25th Season-Programs, Routine Business, 1975 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M., 1976 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M.-Misc., 1977 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M.-Erwin Brodky Awards-Programs, Reports, Forms, 1968-75 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M.-Background Information: History, By-Laws and Regulations (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M.-Correspondence -Leo Beranek, 1968-73 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M.-Correspondence, 1966-73; undated (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M.-Correspondence, 1974-76 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M.-Officers and Directors, 1974-76 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M.-Evaluation for funding, 1973-74 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M.-How to Raise Money, 1966-71 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: C.S.E.M.-Finances, 1966-77 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: American Choral Directors Association (ACDA)-Catalogs (Box 8)
- Non Smith: ACDA-Committees, 1968-69 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: ACDA-National Convention-Dallas, 1977 (Box 8)
- Non Smith: ACDA-Misc., 1970s (Box 8)
- Non Smith: ACDA-Notes (Box 8)
- Non Smith: MA Council on the Arts and Humanities-Misc., 1967-70s (Box 9)
- Non Smith: MA Council on the Arts and Humanities-Applications, 1972-75 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: UMASS-Trustee Advisory Council on the Fine Arts-Correspondence and notes, 1974; undated (Box 9)
- Non Smith: UMASS-Trustee Advisory Council on the Fine Arts-Reports, 1975 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: UMASS-Trustee Advisory Council on the Fine Arts-Reports, 1976 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: UMASS-Trustee Advisory Council on the Fine Arts, undated (Box 9)
- Non Smith: NYU Sings/Jim Willard (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Conference-Secondary Schools, Wesleyan, Milton, 1957; 1963 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Programs-Voices and Brass (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Conference-Harvard Summer School on "The American Composer & Choral Music", 1953 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Harvard Summer School, 1962 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Harvard Summer School, 1963 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Harvard Speech, 1969 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: International Choral Festival-J.M.Greene and Lincoln Center, 1972 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: International Choral Festival-Lincoln Center, 1974 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Heinrich Schutz-Festival of Music, 1972 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Conference-American Guild of Organists, 1954 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: North Carolina Music Festival, 1954 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: College Music Association-8th Annual Meeting, 1954 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: UC Berkeley, 1964 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: UC Berkeley-Preliminary Graduate Exam, 1962-63 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Stanford Summer Choir, 1960 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Conference-Contemporary Am. Choral Music, 1961 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: USC Fullerton-Lecture to Choral Directors, 1966 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: USC Fullerton I-Repertory and Notes, 1966 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: USC Fullerton II-Medieval and Renaissance, 1966 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: USC Fullerton III-Short Sacred Cantata List, 1966 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: USC Fullerton IV-"Far Out Repertory", 1966 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: USC Fullerton-Address, 1966 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: USC-Seminar, Lecture Notes, 1966 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: The Musicians Assoc. of California Community Colleges, Southern Section-Choral Festival-Correspondence and Program, 1971-72 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Address to the Intercollegiate Music Council, Lehigh Univ., 1966 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Lehigh Univ. Visiting Committee for the Creative Arts, 1971-73 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Erie County Music Festivals, 1969-74 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: University-Wide Choral Festival, Oswego, NY, 1970 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Conference-Josquin, 1971 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Tanglewood Festivals, 1970s (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Aspen Music Festival, 1972 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Workshop in the Performance of Medieval and Renaissance Music, 1972 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Choral Seminar for Women, Emory Univ., 1973 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Music for a Festive Occasion, 1973 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: All Connecticut High School Festival, 1973 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Summer Institute in Medieval Performance, 1975 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Misc. Festivals, 1975 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Ecumenical Choir Concert, 1975 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Johnson State College-Chamber Music Center, Johnson VT-Correspondence, Notations, Programs, Music, Misc., 1976-78 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Symposium on Editing, undated (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Mailing Lists-Boston Organizations (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Kodaly Fellowship Committee, 1968-76 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Alexander Chorale, 1970 (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Music Panel-State Dept. Hong Kong, 1970s (Box 9)
- Non Smith: Dartmouth, 1978 (Box 9)
- Photographs: Travel Slides-Pyramids, Jerusalem to Damascus, Group Travel (Box 10)
  (3 boxes)
- Photographs: Xerox Photo masters of Album, 1890-1977 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Family, 1890-1929 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Iva Dee Hiatt alone and with Family, 1920-29 (Box 10)
- Photographs: with Family, 1930s (Box 10)
- Photographs: Iva Dee Hiatt alone and with Others, 1940s (Box 10)
- Photographs: Iva Dee Hiatt alone and with Others, 1950s (Box 10)
- Photographs: Others, 1950s (Box 10)
- Photographs: Iva Dee Hiatt alone and with Others, 1960s (Box 10)
- Photographs: Others, 1960s (Box 10)
- Photographs: Iva Dee Hiatt with Others, 1970s (Box 10)
- Photographs: Others, 1970s (Box 10)
- Photographs: Iva Dee Hiatt alone, 1977-79 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Iva Dee Hiatt with Others, 1977-79 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Others, 1977-79 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Iva Dee Hiatt, undated (Box 10)
- Photographs: Trips (Box 10)
- Photographs: At Smith (Box 10)
- Photographs: Glee Club, 1953-54 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Glee Club, 1954-55 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Glee Club, 1955-56 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Glee Club, 1957-59 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Glee Club, 1959-60 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Glee Club, 1961-62 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Glee Club (with Princeton), 1963-65 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Glee Club, 1966-67 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Glee Club, 1968-69 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Glee Club, 1969-70 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Glee Club, 1970-71 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Glee Club, 1975-76 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Glee Club, undated (Box 10)
- Photographs: Glee Club, Mixed Choruses, Others, undated (Box 10)
- Photographs: Chamber Singers, European Tour, 1956 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Chamber Singers, 1956; 1960s (Box 10)
- Photographs: Chamber Singers, European Tour, 1961 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Chamber Singers, 1970s (Box 10)
- Photographs: Chamber Singers, undated (Box 10)
- Photographs: Soloists, etc., undated (Box 10)
- Photographs: Smith-Wesleyan Mexico, Mar. 1962 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Luis Berber with Singing Boys, Mexico, 1962 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Mexican Tour, 1962 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Smith College Choir, undated (Box 10)
- Photographs: Smith Colleagues, 1979 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Haydn-Mozart Festival, 1959 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Tanglewood, 1963; 67 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Conference-Johnson State College, 1977; 78; 79 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Reunion-Smith Class of 1954, 1979 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Honors, 1979 (Box 10)
- Photographs: Negatives (Tanglewood and others), 1970s; undated (Box 10)
- Memorabilia: Heineken Boot Mug, undated (Box 11)
- Memorabilia: 2nd Prize: International Competition, Koor Festival Den Haag, Adult Female Division, 1977 (Box 11)
- Memorabilia: 1st Prize: International Competition, Koor Festival Den Haag, Youth Female Division, 1977 (Box 11)
- Memorabilia: Audience Prize: International Competition, Koor Festival Den Haag, Adult Female Division, 1977 (Box 11)
- Memorabilia: Audience Prize: International Competition, Koor Festival Den Haag, Youth Female Division, 1977 (Box 11)
- Memorabilia: Introit for 3-part Women's Chorus by Julie G. Pretzat, 1978 (Box 12)
- Glee Club Scrapbook, 1978-79 (Box 12)
- Scrapbook on black paper, undated (Box 12)
- Academic Sashes (Box 12)
- New England Conservatory Award, 1979 (Box 12)
- Framed picture-Iva Dee Hiatt with G.C. Menotti-6th European Tour, Spoleto Festival, 1961 (Box 12)
- 3 Copper Blocks (Box 12)
- Presentation Trophy to Smith-Princeton Chamber Chorus, South American Tour, 1971 (Box 12)
- Francis Cardinal Koenig Medal to Smith-Princeton Chamber Chorus, 8th European Tour, Vienna, 1968 (Box 12)
- Medal of the Autoname to Smith College Chamber Singers, 11th European Tour, 1976 (Box 12)
- Silver Box labeled Iva Dee Hiatt from Glee Club, 1960-61 (Box 12)
- Silver Box labeled Iva Dee Haitt, Smith College Glee Club, undated (Box 12)
- 1st Prize Adult Female Division, Wales, 1958 (Box 12)
- Award-Comune Di Venzia-Assessorato Allo Sport E Turismo (Box 13)
- Award-Llangollen Eisteddfod Internationnes-Smith College Singers (Box 13)
- Award-Llangollen Eisteddfod Internationnes-Smith College Chamber Singers (Box 13)
- Award-LLangollen International Music Eisteddfod-Smith College Singers, 1958 (Box 13)
- Award-Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts-Smith College Chamber Singers, 1965 (Box 13)
- Award-Ami De Parie, 1951 (Box 13)
- Award-U.S. Department of State-Smith College Glee Club, 1958 (Box 13)
- Award-Iva Dee Haitt Honorary Lifetime Membership in Smith College Glee Club (Box 13)
- Award-Regents of University of California-Bachelors of Art in Music, 1941 (Box 13)
- Award-Regents of University of California-Masters of Art in Music, 1948 (Box 13)
- Award-Amherst College, 1979 (Box 13)
- Award-International Koor Festival-Smith College Chamber Singers, 1977 (Box 13)
- Poster-Lucnica Choir (Box 13)
- Poster-Evening of Viennese Music, 1979 (Box 13)
- Posters-Amherst and Smith College Singers (Box 13)
  (2 posters)
- Poster-Quart Festival Dei Due Monde (Box 13)
- Poster-Ottavo Festival Dei Due Monde, 1965 (Box 13)
- Poster-Haydn, Bach and Verdi-Smith College & Amherst College Glee Club and 5 College Festival Orchestra, 1975 (Box 13)
- Poster-Smith and Amherst College Singers in Rome (Box 13)
- Poster-Amerika Haus Munchen (Box 13)
- Poster-Mattaus Passion, 1973 (Box 13)
- Poster-Smith College Chamber Singers, 1976 (Box 13)
- Poster-Smith/Princeton-European Tour (Box 13)
- Poster-Mozart's Requiem, 1976 (Box 13)
- Poster-5 College International University Choral Festival Concert, 1972 (Box 13)
- Poster-Smith College Glee Club, 1975 (Box 13)
- Poster-International Koor Festival, 1977 (Box 13)
- Poster-Smith College Chamber Singers, 1975 (Box 13)
- Photograph-Mattaus Passion, 1973 (Box 13)
- Photograph-Iva Dee Hiatt's Grandfather's portrait (Box 13)
- Photographs-Church of Rosheim, France (Box 13)
  (2 photographs)
- Programs -Spirit of America in Song and Christmas Service, 1975; 1961 (Box 13)
- Personal-Haitt's communication board (Box 13)
- Scores, songbooks, choral pieces, booklets of music #1 (Box 14)
- Scores, songbooks, choral pieces, booklets of music #2 (Box 15)
- Scores, songbooks, choral pieces, booklets of music #3 (Box 16)
- Scores, songbooks, choral pieces, booklets of music #4 (Box 17)
- Scores, songbooks, choral pieces, booklets of music #5 (Box 18)